=Love Start From Marriage= =Episode 5=
= الحب يبدأ من الزواج = = الحلقة 5 =
Female star Jin Sula allegedly was cheated on.
يُزعم أن النجمة جين سولا تعرضت للخداع.
Her rumored boyfriend immediately married another girl.
تزوج صديقها المشاع على الفور من فتاة أخرى.
(He finally married another woman) Jin Sula posted late night
(تزوج أخيرًا من امرأة أخرى) نشرت جين سولا في وقت متأخر من الليل
'Love does not mean commitment'
الحب لا يعني الالتزام
which sounds very heartbreaking.
الذي يبدو مفجعًا جدًا.
Do people have no bottom line now?
هل الناس ليس لديهم خط النهاية الآن؟
(Oh my god! This woman is too bad.) Paparazzi captured the scene
(يا إلهي! هذه المرأة سيئة للغاية.) استولى المصورون على المشهد
that they met secretly in hotel.
أن التقيا سرا في الفندق.
It was pretty stimulating.
لقد كان محفزًا جدًا.
(Sula is a good girl, how could this man do this to her?)
(سولا فتاة طيبة فكيف يفعل بها هذا الرجل هذا؟)
What's your opinion
ما هو رأيك
about Mr. Gu's marriage
حول زواج السيد قو
since you were his rumored girlfriend?
منذ أن كنت صديقته المشاع؟
(Sula is so kind. You have us, Sula.) May all of Ms. Xia's wishes come true.
(سولا لطيفة جدًا. لديكِنا ، سولا.) أتمنى أن تتحقق كل أمنيات السيدة شيا.
Do you think it was all planned
هل تعتقد أن كل شيء كان مخططًا له
that Ms. Xia married CEO of Gu's?
أن السيدة شيا تزوجت الرئيس التنفيذي لشركة Gu's؟
(The girl was married through proper action!)
(الفتاة تزوجت من خلال العمل السليم!)
(Nonsense! Are you serious?) I did not say that.
(هراء! هل أنت جاد؟) أنا لم أقل ذلك.
Stop guessing.
توقف عن التخمين.
(Curse you! You mistress!)
(اللعنة عليك يا سيدتي!) توقف عن التخمين.
(Sula, don't be sad. We always love you.)
(سولا ، لا تحزن. نحن نحبك دائمًا).
(Jin Sula is the third person!)
(جين سولا هو الشخص الثالث!)
(Gu Chengze never said he loved Jin Sula.)
(لم يقل Gu Chengze أبدًا أنه يحب جين سولا.)
(Stop those bullshit before knowing the truth!)
(توقف عن هذا الهراء قبل معرفة الحقيقة!)
(It's that woman! Shame on her! How dare she show up here!)
(إنها تلك المرأة! عار عليها! كيف تجرؤ على الظهور هنا!)
(Notification: You've been reported as a violation and banned from commenting.)
(إشعار: تم الإبلاغ عن انتهاكك وتم منعك من التعليق.)
How dare you, Gu Chengze.
كيف تجرؤ ، غو تشنغزي.
How dare you two-time me?
كيف تجرؤ على مرتين لي؟
Hi, Rose.
مرحبا روز.
Can I borrow your account?
هل يمكنني استعارة حسابك؟
Too late. I'm banned.
بعد فوات الأوان.  أنا ممنوع.
What? You are banned too?
ماذا؟  أنت ممنوع أيضا؟
Those fans are being crazy.
هؤلاء المشجعين مجانين
I was going to defend you,
كنت سأدافع عنك ،
but was reported as soon as I sent my first comment.
ولكن تم الإبلاغ عنها بمجرد أن أرسلت تعليقي الأول.
I should've written an article before commenting.
كان يجب أن أكتب مقالًا قبل التعليق.
Gu Chengze.
جو تشينجزي.
You read the news?
تقرأ الأخبار؟
What exactly is it with you and Jin Sula?
ما هو بالضبط معك و جين سولا؟
You know how much hate I received on the Internet?
أنت تعرف مقدار الكراهية التي تلقيتها على الإنترنت؟
There's nothing between me and her.
لا يوجد شيء بيني وبينها.
I'll take care of this thing.
سأعتني بهذا الشيء.
Trust me.
صدقني.
I can't take your word for it.
لا أستطيع أخذ كلمتك على محمل الجد.
Prove it.
اثبت ذلك.
I'm so disappointed in you.
أنا محبط للغاية فيك.
Please hear me out.
من فضلك اسمعني.
It's not what you think.
ليست كما تعتقد.
(Finally I have the reason to leave Gu family.)
(أخيرًا لدي سبب لمغادرة عائلة Gu.)
I'm going back to my home.
سأعود إلى منزلي.
I accompany you.
أنا مرافقتك.
I'll have our luggage prepared.
سأجهز أمتعتنا.
No.
رقم.
After what has happened,
بعد ما حدث
I need to explain to my parents.
أحتاج أن أشرح لوالديّ.
You'd better deal with this mess
من الأفضل أن تتعامل مع هذه الفوضى
before you come with me.
قبل أن تأتي معي.
Otherwise, explanation won't help anything.
خلاف ذلك ، لن يساعد الشرح في أي شيء.
I'm back.
لقد عدت.
Can you behave like a fair lady?
هل يمكنك التصرف كسيدة عادلة؟
I'm exhausted from playing your elder daughter these days.
لقد استنفدت من لعب دور ابنتك الكبرى هذه الأيام.
Don't get on my back.
لا تقف على ظهري.
Have you found Qianxun?
هل وجدت Qianxun؟
What am I gonna do?
ماذا سوف أفعل؟
Say something.
قل شيئا.
What are you gonna do now that you're married?
ماذا ستفعل الآن بعد أن تزوجت؟
He wanted to marry Qianxun,
أراد الزواج من Qianxun ،
not me.
ليس انا.
Either way, it's the daughter of Xia's.
في كلتا الحالتين ، إنها ابنة شيا.
What's the difference?
ماهو الفرق؟
You should say this in his face.
يجب أن تقول هذا في وجهه.
Not until our company turns better.
ليس حتى تصبح شركتنا أفضل.
You should go back now.
يجب عليك العودة الآن.
The police is going to find Qianxun.
سوف تجد الشرطة Qianxun.
What if it got exposed?
ماذا لو تم الكشف عنها؟
Have you thought about the consequence?
هل فكرت في النتيجة؟
Have you thought about me?
هل فكرت لي؟
Kevin, tell Department of Public Relations to handle it faster.
كيفن ، أخبر إدارة العلاقات العامة للتعامل معها بشكل أسرع.
Hype with the wedding logs of me and Qianxun.
ضجة مع سجلات الزفاف لي و Qianxun.
If none of them works,
إذا لم يعمل أي منهم ،
expose the scandal of Jin Sula.
فضح فضيحة جين سولا.
Best if it goes up on the trending,
الأفضل إذا ارتفع في الاتجاه ،
so that my wife can see it.
حتى تتمكن زوجتي من رؤيتها.
She's our artist after all,
إنها فنانتنا بعد كل شيء ،
is it the right thing to do?
هو الشيء الصحيح الذي ينبغي عمله؟
Why? You have doubts on me?
لماذا ا؟  لديك شكوك علي؟
No, I don't.
لا أنا لا.
Then what are you doing here?
إذن ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Hold on, one more thing.
انتظر ، شيء آخر.
Do you have tips for pacifying women?
هل لديك نصائح لتهدئة النساء؟
Leave it to me.
اتركه لي.
I'll make sure Mrs. Gu won't be mad at you anymore.
سأتأكد من أن السيدة غو لن تغضب منك بعد الآن.